<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/">
  <channel>
    <title>Beginner on Peanuts Code</title>
    <link>https://www.peanuts-code.com/en/tags/beginner/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Beginner on Peanuts Code</description>
    <image>
      <title>Peanuts Code</title>
      <url>https://www.peanuts-code.com/images/logomark.png</url>
      <link>https://www.peanuts-code.com/images/logomark.png</link>
    </image>
    <generator>Hugo -- 0.134.1</generator>
    <language>en</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Wed, 11 May 2022 02:05:00 +0900</lastBuildDate>
    <atom:link href="https://www.peanuts-code.com/en/tags/beginner/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>📔 Game development starting with something simple</title>
      <link>https://www.peanuts-code.com/en/posts/post0002_development_starts_small/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 11 May 2022 02:05:00 +0900</pubDate>
      <guid>https://www.peanuts-code.com/en/posts/post0002_development_starts_small/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;This article is especially worth reading if you are a beginner who has just started or is thinking about starting game development. We hope you will read it through to the end.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;br/&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Now, do you have a dream game that you really want to make? Many people who have started or are thinking of starting game development probably dream of such a game. And that game will have plenty of elements of games that you have played and been influenced by in your life.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;As you can probably guess, this article is now going to make the claim that you should save your dream game for the future. However, this assertion is not brand new, but rather a rather common piece of advice for novice game developers. Let me explain why you should save your dream game for the future.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;br/&gt;
&lt;h2 id=&#34;elements-that-tend-to-be-included-in-the-dream-game&#34;&gt;Elements that tend to be included in the dream game&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;What elements tend to be included in a dream game? By the way, the elements here are the specifications and functions of the game. The following is a list of those that come to mind as examples.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>📔 Age Doesn&#39;t Matter When You Start Game Development</title>
      <link>https://www.peanuts-code.com/en/posts/post0001_no_matter_how_old/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 16 Jan 2022 16:56:41 +0900</pubDate>
      <guid>https://www.peanuts-code.com/en/posts/post0001_no_matter_how_old/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;Many people want to start game development but tend to give up because of their age. No, this is not limited to game development but can be applied to anything from playing the piano to being a YouTuber.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;For some reason, it is a common perception that when you reach middle age, your physical and mental strength declines somehow. However, this is not true. There is no evidence that this socially accepted notion applies to you. It doesn&amp;rsquo;t matter if you are a middle-aged businessman, a first-grader, or a 90-year-old. The moment you decide you want to do something is the youngest time to start doing it.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;In the end, life is about doing or not doing. At the age of 100 years of life, there are few cases where it is too late to start doing something. It would be a shame to make a decision based only on a vague impression that game development sounds too difficult for you. You will never know the truth until you try it.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;It is a fact that game development is often thought of as a hurdle for the average person. When inexperienced people hear the word &amp;ldquo;game development,&amp;rdquo; they tend to imagine that they have to learn to program, that they don&amp;rsquo;t have a sense of design, that they can&amp;rsquo;t compose music, and so on. This impression of &amp;ldquo;difficult&amp;rdquo; gets stronger with age.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
