<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/">
  <channel>
    <title>IndieDev on Peanuts Code</title>
    <link>https://www.peanuts-code.com/en/tags/indiedev/</link>
    <description>Recent content in IndieDev on Peanuts Code</description>
    <image>
      <title>Peanuts Code</title>
      <url>https://www.peanuts-code.com/105</url>
      <link>https://www.peanuts-code.com/105</link>
    </image>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Wed, 03 Apr 2024 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://www.peanuts-code.com/en/tags/indiedev/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Lovely Solitaire</title>
      <link>https://www.peanuts-code.com/en/portfolio/work0002_lovely_solitaire/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 03 Apr 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.peanuts-code.com/en/portfolio/work0002_lovely_solitaire/</guid>
      <description>Introducing a Mobile Game, Lovely Solitaire! When it comes to solitaire (Klondike), it&amp;rsquo;s the king of classic one-player card games, and now, introducing the mobile game &amp;ldquo;Lovely Solitaire&amp;rdquo; available on the App Store! With its chic user interface, you can exude a sense of style even while playing on the train! (Or so we hope?) New to the game? Don&amp;rsquo;t worry, you can learn the rules and tips from the &amp;ldquo;How to Play&amp;rdquo; section in the game!
What Makes It Lovely? The pastel-colored UI and pixel art card designs make it lovely! Plus, the music is incredibly cool, the sound effects when moving cards are satisfying, making it lovely!</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Devlog: Slashing Samurai - Planning</title>
      <link>https://www.peanuts-code.com/en/posts/post0005_slashing_samurai_devlogs/slashing_samurai_devlog_1/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 24 Dec 2023 02:21:00 +0900</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.peanuts-code.com/en/posts/post0005_slashing_samurai_devlogs/slashing_samurai_devlog_1/</guid>
      <description>This article is a record of the &amp;ldquo;Planning&amp;rdquo; phase of the (post-release) devlog of the iOS mobile game &amp;ldquo;Slashing Samurai,&amp;rdquo; released on the App Store on December 15, 2023.
Slashing Samurai is available for free download on the App Store. Just click the banner below to get this game!
Defining the Rough Specifications of the Game The development process began by roughly defining the specifications of the game to be developed.
It was pre-determined that the game would be distributed globally on a specific platform. If aiming for global distribution, it was clear that it would require a certain level of quality to gain approval.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Devlog: Slashing Samurai - Reflection</title>
      <link>https://www.peanuts-code.com/en/posts/post0005_slashing_samurai_devlogs/slashing_samurai_devlog_4/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 11 Jan 2024 00:00:00 +0900</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.peanuts-code.com/en/posts/post0005_slashing_samurai_devlogs/slashing_samurai_devlog_4/</guid>
      <description>This article is a record of reflections on the (post-release) development log of the iOS mobile game &amp;ldquo;Slashing Samurai,&amp;rdquo; released on the App Store on December 15, 2023. It explores areas for improvement and lessons learned during the development process.
Feel free to download &amp;ldquo;Slashing Samurai&amp;rdquo; for free from the App Store using the banner below if you&amp;rsquo;re interested.
Identification of Reflection Points After completing the development of &amp;ldquo;Slashing Samurai&amp;rdquo; and reflecting on the process and outcomes, various points for improvement became apparent. To better utilize these reflections in future game development, I want to document them thoroughly.
Let&amp;rsquo;s start by summarizing specific points for improvement:</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Devlog: Slashing Samurai - Logic</title>
      <link>https://www.peanuts-code.com/en/posts/post0005_slashing_samurai_devlogs/slashing_samurai_devlog_3/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 31 Dec 2023 04:00:00 +0900</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.peanuts-code.com/en/posts/post0005_slashing_samurai_devlogs/slashing_samurai_devlog_3/</guid>
      <description>This article is a record of the &amp;ldquo;logic&amp;rdquo; behind the development of &amp;ldquo;Slashing Samurai,&amp;rdquo; a mobile game for iOS released on the App Store on December 15, 2023, using the Godot Engine. However, to avoid excessive length, specific code details will be kept to a minimum. Slashing Samurai is available for free download on the App Store. Just click the banner below to get this game! Identifying Necessary Screens I am the type to prioritize visuals. In game development, including the creation of &amp;ldquo;Slashing Samurai&amp;rdquo; in Godot, I started by identifying the necessary screens. I also considered the flow of</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Devlog: Slashing Samurai - Assets</title>
      <link>https://www.peanuts-code.com/en/posts/post0005_slashing_samurai_devlogs/slashing_samurai_devlog_2/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 27 Dec 2023 12:00:00 +0900</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.peanuts-code.com/en/posts/post0005_slashing_samurai_devlogs/slashing_samurai_devlog_2/</guid>
      <description>This article is a record of the &amp;ldquo;Assets&amp;rdquo; in the (post) devlog of the iOS mobile game &amp;ldquo;Slashing Samurai,&amp;rdquo; released on the App Store on December 15, 2023.
Slashing Samurai is available for free download on the App Store. Just click the banner below to get this game!
Consideration of Assets to Use In this development log, we record how we prepared assets for the development of the mobile game &amp;ldquo;Slashing Samurai.&amp;rdquo; In the context of game development, assets refer to the materials used.
First, we listed the necessary assets and proceeded with a rough policy to prepare them with as low a budget as possible, considering the time cost.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Grow with game jams</title>
      <link>https://www.peanuts-code.com/en/posts/post0004_my_first_game_jam/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 04 Sep 2022 00:35:00 +0900</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.peanuts-code.com/en/posts/post0004_my_first_game_jam/</guid>
      <description>I recently joined the &amp;ldquo;KENNEY Game Jam&amp;rdquo; held recently. It was my first game jam. In this article, I would like to write about the game jam for indie game developers held on the itch.io website, including what I learned and felt while participating in the game jam. What is a Game Jam? A game jam is an event where participants develop a game in a short period of time, publish it, and evaluate each other. It is also called the hackathon of game development. The itch.io site sells games, assets, and hosts a number of game jams worldwide. Some</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>How to avoid frustration of game development</title>
      <link>https://www.peanuts-code.com/en/posts/post0003_how_to_avoid_frustration/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 04 Jul 2022 08:45:00 +0900</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.peanuts-code.com/en/posts/post0003_how_to_avoid_frustration/</guid>
      <description>When one has taken the trouble to start a personal game development project, one would like to continue it for a long and enjoyable time if possible. However, in general, game development tends to be frustrating. Let us first consider the reasons for this. Reasons for frustration First, game development is hard work. It is sometimes referred to as a comprehensive art form. In other words, a game is a work of art that combines music, images, characters, scenarios, systems, level design, and everything else into one. There is no way it is easy. It is so difficult that it</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Game development starting with something simple</title>
      <link>https://www.peanuts-code.com/en/posts/post0002_development_starts_small/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 11 May 2022 02:05:00 +0900</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.peanuts-code.com/en/posts/post0002_development_starts_small/</guid>
      <description>This article is especially worth reading if you are a beginner who has just started or is thinking about starting game development. We hope you will read it through to the end.
Now, do you have a dream game that you really want to make? Many people who have started or are thinking of starting game development probably dream of such a game. And that game will have plenty of elements of games that you have played and been influenced by in your life.
As you can probably guess, this article is now going to make the claim that you should save your dream game for the future.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Age Doesn&#39;t Matter When You Start Game Development</title>
      <link>https://www.peanuts-code.com/en/posts/post0001_no_matter_how_old/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 16 Jan 2022 16:56:41 +0900</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.peanuts-code.com/en/posts/post0001_no_matter_how_old/</guid>
      <description>Many people want to start game development but tend to give up because of their age. No, this is not limited to game development but can be applied to anything from playing the piano to being a YouTuber.
For some reason, it is a common perception that when you reach middle age, your physical and mental strength declines somehow. However, this is not true. There is no evidence that this socially accepted notion applies to you. It doesn&amp;rsquo;t matter if you are a middle-aged businessman, a first-grader, or a 90-year-old. The moment you decide you want to do something is the youngest time to start doing it.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
