<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/">
  <channel>
    <title>Top-Down on Peanuts Code</title>
    <link>https://www.peanuts-code.com/en/tags/top-down/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Top-Down on Peanuts Code</description>
    <image>
      <title>Peanuts Code</title>
      <url>https://www.peanuts-code.com/images/logomark.png</url>
      <link>https://www.peanuts-code.com/images/logomark.png</link>
    </image>
    <generator>Hugo -- 0.133.0</generator>
    <language>en</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Sat, 28 May 2022 18:41:00 +0900</lastBuildDate>
    <atom:link href="https://www.peanuts-code.com/en/tags/top-down/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>🤖 Homing Missiles in Godot3</title>
      <link>https://www.peanuts-code.com/en/tutorials/gd0008_homing_missiles/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 28 May 2022 18:41:00 +0900</pubDate>
      <guid>https://www.peanuts-code.com/en/tutorials/gd0008_homing_missiles/</guid>
      <description>In this tutorial, we will create a homing missile in a 2D top-down shooter. A homing missile is a missile that tracks its target. Environment This tutorial was created in the following environment ・Godot version: 3.4.2 ・Computer OS version: macOS 11.6.5 To focus on the creation of the homing missile, the rest of the project has been pre-created in advance. The project file for this tutorial is located at GitHub repository . After downloading the .zip file, import the &amp;ldquo;project.godot&amp;rdquo; file in the &amp;ldquo;Start&amp;rdquo; folder into the Godot Engine, and you can start the project with only the preliminary work completed. If you would like to see the completed project in a hurry, import the &amp;ldquo;project.godot&amp;rdquo; file from the &amp;ldquo;End&amp;rdquo; folder. All the assets imported into the project were downloaded from KENNEY website. I used an asset pack called Tower Defense (top-down) . I just want to thank them for making such a great asset pack available to the public. Preliminary Preparation The following game specifications, except</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>🤖 Bullet Hell in Godot3</title>
      <link>https://www.peanuts-code.com/en/tutorials/gd0007_bullethell/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 23 May 2022 01:30:00 +0900</pubDate>
      <guid>https://www.peanuts-code.com/en/tutorials/gd0007_bullethell/</guid>
      <description>In this time, we will create a bullet hell aka barrage for a barrage shooting game. The bullet hell is a large number of bullets (or similar long-range attacks) like a curtain. A &amp;ldquo;bullet hell shooter&amp;rdquo; is a game in which the player shoots at and defeats enemy characters while dodging and weaving through the gaps between the bullets. Some games specialize in simply dodging the bullets. Many games are based on the motif of spaceships and fighter planes that fit the image (in this tutorial, a ground battle between a wizard and a monster though).
In this tutorial, we will focus only on creating a bullet hell. Also, while bullet hell come in various shapes and sizes, we will focus on rotating-type bullet hell.
Environment This tutorial was created in the following environment
・Godot version: 3.4.2
・Computer OS version: macOS 11.6.5
The project file for this tutorial is located at GitHub repository . After downloading the .zip file, import the &amp;ldquo;project.godot&amp;rdquo; file in the &amp;ldquo;Start&amp;rdquo; folder into the Godot Engine, and you will be able to start with a project that has only been prepped.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>🤖 Four Types of Guns for Top-down Shooting in Godot3</title>
      <link>https://www.peanuts-code.com/en/tutorials/gd0006_guns_of_topdown_shooter/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 07 May 2022 22:05:00 +0900</pubDate>
      <guid>https://www.peanuts-code.com/en/tutorials/gd0006_guns_of_topdown_shooter/</guid>
      <description>In this tutorial, we are going to make four types of guns that commonly appear in 2D top-down shooters. Specifically, they are as follows. Handgun Shotgun Machine gun Laser Gun Environment This tutorial was created in the following environment ・Godot version: 3.4.2 ・Computer OS version: macOS 11.6.5 Since this tutorial will focus on gun creation, the following has been prepared in advance. 1. Game world A scene called &amp;ldquo;World.tscn&amp;rdquo; was prepared, and the appearance was simply created by adding a &amp;ldquo;TileMap&amp;rdquo; node. In addition to the &amp;ldquo;TileMap&amp;rdquo; node, a &amp;ldquo;Player&amp;rdquo; node and several &amp;ldquo;Obstacle&amp;rdquo; nodes were added. For these, we created individual scenes and added the instances. 2. Player Character Created as &amp;ldquo;Player.tscn&amp;rdquo; scene. The root node is the &amp;ldquo;KinematicBody2D&amp;rdquo; class, and the &amp;ldquo;Sprite&amp;rdquo; and the &amp;ldquo;CollisionShape2D&amp;rdquo; were added as child nodes. The texture of the &amp;ldquo;Sprite&amp;rdquo; node is a hitman with a gun. A node named &amp;ldquo;Muzzle&amp;rdquo; of the &amp;ldquo;Position2D&amp;rdquo; class was placed at the tip of the image of the gun held by the hitman.</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
