<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/">
  <channel>
    <title>Shooter on Peanuts Code</title>
    <link>https://www.peanuts-code.com/en/tags/shooter/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Shooter on Peanuts Code</description>
    <image>
      <title>Peanuts Code</title>
      <url>https://www.peanuts-code.com/105</url>
      <link>https://www.peanuts-code.com/105</link>
    </image>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Sat, 28 May 2022 18:41:00 +0900</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://www.peanuts-code.com/en/tags/shooter/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>🤖 Homing Missiles in Godot3</title>
      <link>https://www.peanuts-code.com/en/tutorials/gd0008_homing_missiles/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 28 May 2022 18:41:00 +0900</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.peanuts-code.com/en/tutorials/gd0008_homing_missiles/</guid>
      <description>In this tutorial, we will create a homing missile in a 2D top-down shooter. A homing missile is a missile that tracks its target. Environment This tutorial was created in the following environment ・Godot version: 3.4.2 ・Computer OS version: macOS 11.6.5 To focus on the creation of the homing missile, the rest of the project has been pre-created in advance. The project file for this tutorial is located at GitHub repository . After downloading the .zip file, import the &amp;ldquo;project.godot&amp;rdquo; file in the &amp;ldquo;Start&amp;rdquo; folder into the</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>🤖 Bullet Hell in Godot3</title>
      <link>https://www.peanuts-code.com/en/tutorials/gd0007_bullethell/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 23 May 2022 01:30:00 +0900</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.peanuts-code.com/en/tutorials/gd0007_bullethell/</guid>
      <description>In this time, we will create a bullet hell aka barrage for a barrage shooting game. The bullet hell is a large number of bullets (or similar long-range attacks) like a curtain. A &amp;ldquo;bullet hell shooter&amp;rdquo; is a game in which the player shoots at and defeats enemy characters while dodging and weaving through the gaps between the bullets. Some games specialize in simply dodging the bullets. Many games are based on the motif of spaceships and fighter planes that fit the image (in this tutorial, a ground battle between a wizard and a monster though).
In this tutorial, we will focus only on creating a bullet hell.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>🤖 Four Types of Guns for Top-down Shooting in Godot3</title>
      <link>https://www.peanuts-code.com/en/tutorials/gd0006_guns_of_topdown_shooter/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 07 May 2022 22:05:00 +0900</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.peanuts-code.com/en/tutorials/gd0006_guns_of_topdown_shooter/</guid>
      <description>In this tutorial, we are going to make four types of guns that commonly appear in 2D top-down shooters. Specifically, they are as follows. Handgun Shotgun Machine gun Laser Gun Environment This tutorial was created in the following environment ・Godot version: 3.4.2 ・Computer OS version: macOS 11.6.5 Since this tutorial will focus on gun creation, the following has been prepared in advance. 1. Game world A scene called &amp;ldquo;World.tscn&amp;rdquo; was prepared, and the appearance was simply created by adding a &amp;ldquo;TileMap&amp;rdquo; node. In addition to the &amp;ldquo;TileMap&amp;rdquo;</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
