<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/">
  <channel>
    <title>NoExperience on Peanuts Code</title>
    <link>https://www.peanuts-code.com/en/tags/noexperience/</link>
    <description>Recent content in NoExperience on Peanuts Code</description>
    <image>
      <title>Peanuts Code</title>
      <url>https://www.peanuts-code.com/105</url>
      <link>https://www.peanuts-code.com/105</link>
    </image>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Wed, 11 May 2022 02:05:00 +0900</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://www.peanuts-code.com/en/tags/noexperience/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>📔 Game development starting with something simple</title>
      <link>https://www.peanuts-code.com/en/posts/post0002_development_starts_small/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 11 May 2022 02:05:00 +0900</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.peanuts-code.com/en/posts/post0002_development_starts_small/</guid>
      <description>This article is especially worth reading if you are a beginner who has just started or is thinking about starting game development. We hope you will read it through to the end.
Now, do you have a dream game that you really want to make? Many people who have started or are thinking of starting game development probably dream of such a game. And that game will have plenty of elements of games that you have played and been influenced by in your life.
As you can probably guess, this article is now going to make the claim that you should save your dream game for the future.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>📔 Age Doesn&#39;t Matter When You Start Game Development</title>
      <link>https://www.peanuts-code.com/en/posts/post0001_no_matter_how_old/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 16 Jan 2022 16:56:41 +0900</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.peanuts-code.com/en/posts/post0001_no_matter_how_old/</guid>
      <description>Many people want to start game development but tend to give up because of their age. No, this is not limited to game development but can be applied to anything from playing the piano to being a YouTuber.
For some reason, it is a common perception that when you reach middle age, your physical and mental strength declines somehow. However, this is not true. There is no evidence that this socially accepted notion applies to you. It doesn&amp;rsquo;t matter if you are a middle-aged businessman, a first-grader, or a 90-year-old. The moment you decide you want to do something is the youngest time to start doing it.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
