<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/">
  <channel>
    <title>Works on Peanuts Code</title>
    <link>https://www.peanuts-code.com/en/portfolio/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Works on Peanuts Code</description>
    <image>
      <title>Peanuts Code</title>
      <url>https://www.peanuts-code.com/105</url>
      <link>https://www.peanuts-code.com/105</link>
    </image>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Wed, 03 Apr 2024 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://www.peanuts-code.com/en/portfolio/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Lovely Solitaire</title>
      <link>https://www.peanuts-code.com/en/portfolio/work0002_lovely_solitaire/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 03 Apr 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.peanuts-code.com/en/portfolio/work0002_lovely_solitaire/</guid>
      <description>Introducing a Mobile Game, Lovely Solitaire! When it comes to solitaire (Klondike), it&amp;rsquo;s the king of classic one-player card games, and now, introducing the mobile game &amp;ldquo;Lovely Solitaire&amp;rdquo; available on the App Store! With its chic user interface, you can exude a sense of style even while playing on the train! (Or so we hope?) New to the game? Don&amp;rsquo;t worry, you can learn the rules and tips from the &amp;ldquo;How to Play&amp;rdquo; section in the game!
What Makes It Lovely? The pastel-colored UI and pixel art card designs make it lovely! Plus, the music is incredibly cool, the sound effects when moving cards are satisfying, making it lovely!</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Slashing Samurai</title>
      <link>https://www.peanuts-code.com/en/portfolio/work0001_slashing_samurai/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 30 Nov 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.peanuts-code.com/en/portfolio/work0001_slashing_samurai/</guid>
      <description>Casual Timing Game, Slashing Samurai, is Here! Push beyond the limits of your dynamic visual acuity! Let a samurai to slice falling objects mid-air! Thrilling and addictive casual timing game – Can play now!
Your browser does not support the video tag. Overview This is a exciting timing game! In each stage, a single object (a donut, a stuffed animal, a tomato, a bicycle, a statue, and more from different eras and places!) falls from the sky. Using touch-and-release controls, make the pixelated samurai jump and skillfully cut the falling item to clear the stage.
Download on App Store for free Slashing Samurai is available for free download on the App Store.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
